Eric Bower
Personal email: ebower42@gmail.com
IU email: epbower@iu.edu
Cell: (513) 432-6185

To me, engineering is using creativity and the knowledge of science to create physical objects.  These objects are often innovative and have useful applications to the world.

Intelligent Systems Engineering is the engineering of a device that can scan and analyze the world around it.  When it does that, it decides what to do to its surroundings based on complicated algorithms. 

As an engineer in ISE, I would like to be able to skillfully build a device on my own, which includes hardware and software.  I would like this device to be a useful device for others.

I think I need to be innovative and creative for me to be the engineer I want to be.  I also need to be skilled in programming and hardware building.